[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "Which player had his jersey retired by the Miami Heat?",
        "a" : "Michael Jordan",
        "b" : "Pete Maravich",
        "c" : "Bam Adebayo",
        "d" : "Chris Webber",
        "answer" : "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Who has the most blocks in an NBA career?",
        "a" : "David Robinson",
        "b" : "Shaquille O'Neal",
        "c" : "Hakeem Olajuwon",
        "d" : "Elmore Smith",
        "answer" : "c"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "Who has the most blocks in an NBA game?",
        "a" : "David Robinson",
        "b" : "Shaquille O'Neal",
        "c" : "Hakeem Olajuwon",
        "d" : "Elmore Smith",
        "answer" : "d"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "Which NBA player when to Texas University?",
        "a" : "Kevin Durant",
        "b" : "Bradley Beal",
        "c" : "Pascal Siakam",
        "d" : "Eric Bledsoe",
        "answer" : "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "Which college did CJ McCollum go?",
        "a" : "Weber State",
        "b" : "Lehigh",
        "c" : "Ohio State",
        "d" : "Michigan",
        "answer" : "b"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Who is the leading scorer of all time?",
        "a" : "Michael Jordan",
        "b" : "Kareem-Abdul Jabbar",
        "c" : "Wilt Chamberlain",
        "d" : "Kobe Bryant",
        "answer" : "b"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "How many championships did Kobe Bryant win?",
        "a" : "3",
        "b" : "4",
        "c" : "5",
        "d" : "6",
        "answer" : "c"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "How many 3 pointers did Ray Allen make in his career?",
        "a" : "2,973",
        "b" : "2,560",
        "c" : "2,495",
        "d" : "3,223",
        "answer" : "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "Which of these players have the most runner-up MVPs (second votes) but have never won an MVP?",
        "a" : "George Gervin",
        "b" : "Bob McAdoo",
        "c" : "Jerry West",
        "d" : "Oscar Robertson",
        "answer" : "c"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "How many times has Michael Jordan led the league in scoring?",
        "a" : "9 times",
        "b" : "10 times",
        "c" : "11 times",
        "d" : "12 times",
        "answer" : "b"
    }    
]